

NỀN TẢNG TUYỂN DỤNG NHÂN SỰ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Ứng viên Duy N. | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn





Duy N.

Android Developer

August 02, 1990

[protected data]

Pham Hung Street, Cau Giay District, Hanoi, Vietnam Male

% [protected data]

PROFILE

Experienced Android Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Mobile Applications, Java, Android Development, Kotlin, and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science.

SKILLS

Android Java

Android Kotlin

Flutter

INTERESTS

Read book Listen music Watch movie Play billiards

EDUCATION

Troy University (Oct 2014 > Jan 2019)

Major: Computer Science

Degree: Bachelor

WORK EXPERIENCE

CO-WELL Asia (Mar 2019 > Present)

Android Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Develop and maintain Android applications for Vietnamese and Japanese customers.
- Some featured projects have participated in developing (published on Google Play): AEONMALL Vietnam, Aeonmall Vietnam Tenants, MyGOLFTEC GDO

Introduce the projects involved and the role in the project:

- AEONMALL Vietnam (joined from Sep 2019 to present): This application is developed to support customers to update the latest information at malls of AEON MALL Vietnam. My role in the project is that the android developer develops and maintains the native application Android to run on Android devices.
- Aeonmall Vietnam Tenants (joined from Sep 2019 to present): This application is developed to support tenants in managing cooperative campaigns with AEON MALL Vietnam. My role in the project is that the android developer supports developing the hybrid application to run on both Android and iOS devices.
- MyGOLFTEC GDO (joined from Aug 2019 to July 2020): This application is developed to help students of the GOLFTEC system (the system of the studios that training golf of GDO company in Japan) accesses to use GOLFTEC system services. My role in the project is that the android developer develops and maintains the native application to run on Android devices.

Recognition and Gains:
- The project I participated in developing won the company's 2019 MVP award.
(AEONMALL Vietnam project)